Guide to the Institute of Human Relations, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, circa 1928-1963; Accession 19ND-A-159
  - Publications, 1928-1940
    - The Harkness Hoot: a Yale undergraduate review, 1931 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - The Human Welfare Group
      - Book: The Human Welfare Group (Box 64, Folder 11)
      - Recreational facilities, undated (Box 64, Folder 12)
      - Report to the National Advisory Committee, 1930 (Box 64, Folder 13)
      - Series of informal discussions, I-VIII, undated (Box 64, Folder 14)
      - Twelve questions and Answers Yale Proposes to Study Man, 1929 (Box 64, Folder 15)
      - University Club: New York meeting, 1929 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Yale Alumni Weekly: issues on Institute, 1929-1931 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Yale Daily News: Institute dedication issue, 1931 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Yale Daily News: Winternitz article on Institute, 1932 (Box 64)
    - Yale's Institute of Human Relations and The Yale Institute of Human Relations by Angell, James R., 1929-1930 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Yale Laboratories of Comparative Psychology: Yerkes, Robert M., 1932 (Box 64, Folder 20)